Guide to the Doris Duke Papers on the Falcon Lair Residence, 1937-1999 RL.01432
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Doris Duke papers on the Falcon Lair residence
1937-1999
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke, Doris
RL.01432
4.6 Linear Feet
The Falcon Lair residence was purchased by Doris Duke in April, 1953 primarily for use on her occasional visits to California and for use while she was in transit to or from her residence in Honolulu. Compared to her other estates, the residence was not large, however, being located in the hills above Benedict Canyon overlooking Beverly Hills, it served as a retreat from public life. Soon after the home was purchased, Doris Duke hired Tony Duquette to supervise the entire redecoration and remodeling of Falcon Lair. The home was renovated again in the mid-1970s. Miss Duke lived at Falcon Lair until her death in 1993, and in 1998 the property was sold by the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation. The collection is arranged into two series: Administrative Records and Architectural Records. It spans the years 1937 to 1999, beginning with the purchase and interior renovation of the home and ending with maintenance and general upkeep of the home after Doris Duke's death in 1993. The collection primarily documents the expenses and daily operations of renovating, running, and maintaining the Falcon Lair residence, and includes invoices and receipts for services and repairs, correspondence, memoranda, and telegrams relating to routine matters of the residence, expenses, and photo inventories of furniture, fixtures, and other household items. A majority of the architectural records detail alterations and additions to the Falcon Lair residence.
3,285 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use. Due to the fragility of the architectural records, The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Doris Duke Papers on the Falcon Lair Residence were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a donation from the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation in June 2009.
Historical Note
The Falcon Lair residence was purchased by Doris Duke in April, 1953 primarily for use on her occasional visits to California and for use while she was in transit to or from her residence in Honolulu. Compared to her other estates, the residence was not large, however, being located in the hills above Benedict Canyon overlooking Beverly Hills, it served as a retreat from public life. Soon after the home was purchased, Doris Duke hired Tony Duquette to supervise the entire redecoration and remodeling of Falcon Lair. The home was renovated again in the mid-1970s. Miss Duke lived at Falcon Lair until her death in 1993, and in 1998 the property was sold by the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation.
Collection Overview
The Doris Duke papers on the Falcon Lair residence (formerly FL.5) are part of the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation Historical Archives which were donated to the Duke University. David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library by the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation. The collection is arranged into two series: Administrative Records and Architectural Records. It spans the years 1937 to 1999, beginning with the purchase and interior renovation of the home and ending with maintenance and general upkeep of the home after Doris Duke's death in 1993. The collection primarily documents the expenses and daily operations of renovating, running, and maintaining the Falcon Lair residence, and includes invoices and receipts for services and repairs, correspondence, memoranda, and telegrams relating to routine matters of the residence, expenses, and photo inventories of furniture, fixtures, and other household items. A majority of the architectural records detail alterations and additions to the Falcon Lair residence. The materials in this collection are arranged in chronological order and alphabetically there under.
Related Material
Duke Family New York Apartments Collection, 1908-1997
Duke University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Doris Duke Papers on the Shangri La Residence, 1932-2003
Duke University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Doris Duke Papers on the Rough Point Residence, 1922-1997
Duke University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Architecture -- Designs and plans; California; Architectural drawing -- United States -- 20th century; Duke, Doris; Duke, Doris
- Administrative Records, 1943-1999
  Scope and Contents note
  Topics in this series are widely varied; however they are all related to the Falcon Lair residence. Materials include correspondence and memoranda, estimates and invoices for interior decorating services, renovations and repairs to the home, and inventories of household items (many with color and B&W photographs). A majority of the correspondence is from employees regarding the daily activities of Falcon Lair, including the hiring of temporary help, payment of invoices/bills, wages, repairs and services to house, and other transactions. While much of the correspondence is related to the business side of Falcon Lair, the personal side of life is also reflected as the authors often comment on current events and other activities.
  - Invoices for purchase of and shipment of tables to Falcon Lair. 1943, 1953, 1955, 1962, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Invoices for purchase of lanterns, candlesticks, chandeliers, and lamps with shades. 1943, 1955, 1958, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Invoices for purchase of various furniture and household items including but not limited to tables, rugs, paintings, carved doors, tapestries, and antique Roman pottery jars. Includes invoice for purchase of 153 volumes of literature by Emerson, Milton, Hardy, Kipling, Scott, Stevenson, and Tolstoy. These volumes were put up for sale at the Christie's 2004 auction as items #2314–2319. 1943, 1953–1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Inventory, Falcon Lair. Copies, compiled on June 28, 1988. Receipts. 1940s–1970s (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Invoices and memoranda regarding alterations made to the Falcon Lair Playhouse. Includes contract with J.H. Kuhl & Sons to paint and connect utilities in the Playhouse (1953). Also includes invoices for furnishings purchased by Tony Duquette. 1952–1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Invoice for purchase of an Italian urn with hand carved mouldings. June 16, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and maps relating to vacation of portion of Bella Drive, tentative Map No. 19896. Materials between Harvey G. Chapman Land Surveyor, and Doris Duke c/o Johnny Gomez and S. Hawkins, Doris Duke's attorney. Includes report of Survey No. 5310. 1953–1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence relating to remodeling, redecorating, and upkeep of Falcon Lair. 1953–1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and telegrams mainly between Johnny Gomez, S.L. Hawkins, and Agnes Brown regarding the payment of various expenses at Falcon Lair. Includes telegrams sent from Johnny Gomez to S.L. Hawkins requesting money deposits in his bank account. 1953–1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invoices and memoranda pertaining to repair the roof, main house, and Playhouse at Falcon Lair. Includes invoices for telephone and grocery story accounts as well. 1953, 1966–1968, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Invoices for benches and chairs purchased for Falcon Lair. Includes fabric samples. 1953–1955, 1963, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Invoices for furniture and services performed at Falcon Lair. Includes some purchases by Doris Duke and Johnny Gomez. 1953-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Invoices for interior design work performed at Falcon Lair by Edward Tirella and Tony Duquette. Includes purchase of rugs, an antique Tehran and a silk Keshan. 1953, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Invoice for Keshaw rug purchased by Johnny Gomez for Falcon Lair. October 26, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Invoices for purchase of musical instruments such as three Steinway pianos, an antique bassoon, an Italian lute, a Japanese lute, and stereo equipment. 1953–1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Invoices for restoration work performed on paintings residing at Falcon Lair. Paintings restored include Botticelli, Lucatelli/Benezech, “Campagne de Grece,” and Vernet/le Veau, “Isle de l'Archipel.” Includes invoice for purchase of an evening cape, earrings, Indian Emerald beads, and seed Pearl. 1953, 1955, 1959, 1963–1965, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Inventory of materials and objects located at 1436 Bella Dr., Beverly Hills, CA.1953–1965, 1973–1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Invoices to Tony Duquette, decorator supervising remodeling of Falcon Lair, paid by Doris Duke, office at 30 Rockefeller Plaza. File includes copy of letter to S.L. Hawkins from Tony Duquette reviewing and confirming his Agreement for employment April 9, 1953. 1953–1954 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Inventory for items at Falcon Lair such as rugs, carpets, chinoises, and other household items, 1954-1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Inventory of furniture and fixtures at 1436 Bella Dr., Beverly Hills, CA. Includes letter to Johnny Gomez from S.L. Hawkins (February 2, 1954). 1954 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Invoices for furniture and clothing purchases as well as utility bills. Includes correspondence between Agnes Brown, 30 Rockefeller, N.Y., N.Y., and Lucille Thomas, Falcon Lair, regarding accounts payable for Falcon Lair. Also includes Grant Deed between Russell A. McKinnon and Doris Duke conveying Lot 11 of Tract No. 6774 to Doris Duke (August 4, 1954). 1954, 1961–1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Invoices for plumbing, electrical, and construction repairs performed at Falcon Lair. Includes invoices from architect Y. Tom Makino and invoices paid by the DBO. 1954–1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Invoices for upholstery modification made to chairs, tables, and a bed at Falcon Lair. 1954, 1958, 1963, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Invoices for electrical repairs made at Falcon Lair. Includes repairs performed on electrical heaters and musical equipment at Falcon Lair. 1955, 1960, 1964–1967, 1973, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Memorandum regarding property tax on the Falcon Lair property. Includes Property Statement Form No. 2 from Los Angeles County, California for the Falcon Lair property. 1955–1956, 1959–1960, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Monthly expense accounts for Falcon Lair. 1956–1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and estimates from A.A. Hokom Co., plumbing service, for installation of a Steam Room, water softener, and repairs to the sprinkler system at Falcon Lair. Includes a Certificate of Insurance with the American Insurance Company in the name of A.A. Hokom Co. 1961–1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and estimates for plumbing repairs made by A.A. Hokom Co. at Falcon Lair. 1962–1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and estimates for roof repairs from architect Y. Tom Makino and the Co-Operative Roof Co. 1962, 1966–1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda, invoices, and receipts for building repairs, various expenses, furnishings, utilities, and vehicles. 1962–1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda regarding the installation of a sprinkler system at Falcon Lair by A.A. Hokom Company. Includes Certificate of Liability Insurance. 1962–1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Signed Contracts and memoranda between Doris Duke and A.A. Hokom Co. for plumbing repairs made at Falcon Lair. 1962–1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Invoice and letter for sale of 1760 Malcolm Ave., Westwood, California, real property, from Doris Duke to Eleanor and John Barber. March 1963–May 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Invoices for purchase of curtains and drapes. 1963–1964, 1982, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda regarding the purchase of 1440 Bella Drive, property behind Falcon Lair, from Mrs. G. Buys. Includes memoranda regarding transfer of land of S.L. and J.B. Hawkins to Doris Duke, Policy No. 3816373. Also includes an appraisal by Farrell F. Wallett for 1440 Bella Drive (February 2, 1965). 1964–1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Invoices for fabric purchased to make a comforter and drapes. 1965, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda from architect Y. Tom Makino to Miss Duke regarding equipment, installation, and construction at Falcon Lair. 1965–1977 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda from architect Y. Tom Makino to Miss Duke regarding equipment, installation, and construction at Falcon Lair. 1965–1977 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda to Charles Allcock from David Rimmer approving the payment of bills involved in operating Falcon Lair. Such memoranda and invoices pertain to grocery and utility bills as well as clothing and pharmaceutical purchases. 1966–1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Inventory of furniture, fixtures, paintings, and other objects at 1436 Bella Dr., Beverly Hills, CA. 1968–1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Inventory, Falcon Lair, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum and homeowner's property tax exemption form. 1968–1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and notices regarding pest control, brush clearance, and accounts payable at Falcon Lair. 1969–1970, 1975–1976, 1986–1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Invoice and voucher for reupholstery of love seats at Falcon Lair by Tony Duquette. 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Invoices relating to work and purchases at Falcon Lair. 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and notices regarding pest control, brush clearance, and accounts payable at Falcon Lair. Includes offers from realtors to purchase Falcon Lair (not solicited by Doris Duke). 1973–1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Inventory of furniture and fixtures of 1436 Bella Dr., Beverly Hills, CA. 1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to daily operations at Falcon Lair. 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda regarding interior design work completed by LADD Interiors. 1976–1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Tax bills for Falcon Lair. 1979, 1981–1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Contracts for pest control at Falcon Lair conducted with the American Termite Control Company. Includes Contracts and proposals for renovations to Falcon Lair to be designed by Makino and Miura Architects. Also includes fabric samples for reupholstery work done at Duke Farms, Shangri La, and Falcon Lair. 1980–1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Inventory cards for fine art and furnishings at Falcon Lair. Most purchases made from Parke-Bernet Galleries, Inc., N.Y.C., 1980–1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Directions for installing a chandelier from the New York Apartment at Falcon Lair. 1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda regarding Tony Duquette teaching at UCLA, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Shipping receipt for shipment of a tape recorder sent from Duke Farms to Falcon Lair. December 22, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from local realtor Bob Dalton, interested in purchasing Falcon Lair (land was not for sale). September 18, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sales Agreement and Contract between Doris Duke and Internal Systems for upgrades made to the security system at Falcon Lair. March 1987–April 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Contract for construction repairs on retaining walls to relieve water pressure at Falcon Lair. Signed by Doris Duke. July 31, 1987 (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Inventory for items at Falcon Lair located in the Entrance Hall, Living Room, Kitchen Hallway, and Playhouse. 1988–1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda regarding new zoning laws in California which did not affect the Falcon Lair property. Includes a copy of the “General Plan/Zoning Consistency Program.” 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Crest [Lair] - Playhouse, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Apartment, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Grounds, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Kitchen, 1988-1989 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Kitchen, 1988-1989 (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Kitchen, 1988-1989 (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Living Room, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Dining Room, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Music Room, 1988-1989 (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Music Room, 1988-1989 (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Hallways, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Miss Duke's Room, 1988-1989 (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Miss Duke's Room, 1988-1989 (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Spanish Room, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Reports pertaining to title surveys conducted by Mitchell Surveys and Commonwealth Land Title Company. Includes a Title Insurance Policy issued for the Falcon Lair property issued by the Commonwealth Land Title Insurance Company. 1989, 1991–1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Entrance hall, downstairs hall, Miss Duke's bedroom/bathroom, Spanish bedroom, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Kitchen hallway, Kitchen breakfast room, China, Silver, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Playhouse, Apartment, Grounds, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Photo inventory of Falcon Lair - Living room, Dining room, Powder room, Music room, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Invoice for monthly security patrol of Falcon Lair by Westec Patrol. Includes printed materials about Westec and company stickers to be displayed on the property. 1990, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Invoices for veterinary services performed on Falcon Lair dogs, Cain, Raquel, and Webster. 1990–1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Certificates of Insurance for Ann Bostich's dog, Foxy, who resided at Falcon Lair. Includes invoices for veterinary treatment as well. 1991–1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with the DBO to purchase Falcon Lair (not solicited by Doris Duke or the DBO). October 14, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Faxed materials sent from Carol Sowden to Irwin Bloom regarding the purchase of a Volvo Wagon for Falcon Lair. Includes an advertisement for a 1991 Volvo Wagon. July 15, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Invoices for cable and telephone service repair calls made at Falcon Lair. Includes contracts and invoices for roofing repairs. 1991, 1994–1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Invoices for installation of a security system, renovations to the septic system, and accounts payable at Falcon Lair. 1991, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Invoices for the purchase of appliances at Falcon Lair. 1991–1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Certificates for Ann Bostich's dog, Robert, who resided at Falcon Lair. Includes invoices for veterinary treatment as well. 1992–1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Inventory of linens, vehicles, appliances, and equipment at Falcon Lair. 1992 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Invoices for veterinary services performed on Falcon Lair dogs. 1992–1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Memoranda and weekly reports from DBO and Duke Farms staff to Miss Duke and Bernard Lafferty while they resided at Falcon Lair and Shangri La. This file was returned from Falcon Lair at the time of Miss Duke's death. 1992–1993 (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Memoranda and weekly reports from DBO and Duke Farms staff to Miss Duke and Bernard Lafferty while they resided at Falcon Lair and Shangri La. This file was returned from Falcon Lair at the time of Miss Duke's death. 1992–1993 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Inventory of rugs, chairs, sofas, and curtains at Falcon Lair (1997). Includes photos and fabric samples used for reupholstered furniture. 1993–1995, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Invoices and credit card receipts for a mattress and bedding at Falcon Lair. April 1993–June 1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Contracts and proposals for Chimney, Patio Bedroom, Bathroom, and Guest House renovations at Falcon Lair. Includes Estate of Doris Duke request forms to pay for each project. 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Invoices for electrical and lighting repairs as well as pest extermination at Falcon Lair. 1994–1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Invoices for installation of a security system at Falcon Lair. Includes printed materials for the security company, Bel-Air Patrol. 1994–1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda from the DBO to Falcon Lair Estate Managers Nuku Makasiale and Robert Toretta. 1994–1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda regarding vacation and hiring policies at Duke Farms. Includes memorandum from Bernard Lafferty directing all DDCF managers not to speak with former employees Ann Bostich, Mariano De Valasco, or Colin Shanley. 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Proposals for repairs made to the septic system and Roof at Falcon Lair. Includes approval for these and other renovations made at Falcon Lair by structural engineer Herman Goodman. 1994–1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Purchase orders for repairs made to a clogged kitchen sink and the replacement of a hot water heater. Includes a Service Agreement for Bernard Lafferty's cell phone. 1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Invoices and memoranda for veterinary services performed on the Falcon Lair dogs. 1995–1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Invoices for vaccinations, medical treatment, and general care for the Falcon Lair dogs and cats. Includes a training brochure for German shepherds. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda and proposals regarding hillside soil remediation at Falcon Lair. 1995, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Memoranda and related materials concerning activities at Falcon Lair and the shipments of goods and animals between DF and FL. 1995–1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Memoranda regarding shipment of cats, Simon and Maxwell, back to Falcon Lair from Duke Farms. Includes Vaccination Certificates for the cats. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Copy of notebook listing service repairs needing to be made at Falcon Lair. Includes phone messages. May be Robert Toretta's notebook. c. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Memoranda from the DBO to Falcon Lair Estate Managers Nuku Makasiale and Robert Toretta. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Falcon Lair stationary. c. 1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Memoranda regarding Falcon Lair after it was sold by the Foundation. 1997, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Memoranda regarding sale of Falcon Lair. Includes a list of potential buyers who viewed the estate. 1997–1998 [Restricted] (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Invoices and memoranda regarding the installation of a new electric water heater at Falcon Lair. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Invoices and memoranda concerning Falcon Lair taxes which were assessed after Falcon Lair had already been sold. Includes copies of the Executor's Deed and the Grant Deed for Falcon Lair. 1999 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - California inventory, invoices (photo copies), 1953-1953 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and related materials regaring alterations made at Falcon Lair, 1953-1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - California inventory, includes photographs, 1953-1959, 1970-1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence regarding work to be performed at Falcon Lair, 1967 Apr 28 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - California residence - old security informatio, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Preliminary findings and recommendations from inspection performed at Falcon Lair, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - California residence correspondence, 1991-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Proposal and contract for repair work at Falcon Lair to be performed by Powell Electric, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)